[
    {
        "question": "He reached a position of ___ during the World Cup in Italy, where he played a remarkable part in the semifinals against the quality opponent.",
        "answer": "prominence"
    },
    {
        "question": "This time, the whole class are listening attentively to my essay, bursting into laughter occasionally, but not in ___ or ridicule.",
        "answer": "contempt"
    },
    {
        "question": "The survey ___ that approximately 20 percent of tennage Internet users become addicated, while the parent's judgment of the situation is not so optimistic.",
        "answer": "estimates"
    },
    {
        "question": "Maybe it's not that __ people see things less realistically, but that people who see things realistically have more reasons to feel blue.",
        "answer": "depressed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Some researchers believed that __ pressure could make you more attentive, improving your memory and ability to learn.",
        "answer": "psychological"
    },
    {
        "question": "As the Ebola virus began to ___ Central and West Africa, uncontrolled panic quickly spread to other areas due to its high fatality rate.",
        "answer": "invade"
    },
    {
        "question": "Although OCD(obsessive-compulsive disorder) is one of the most disabling of psychiatric conditions, it is also one of the most ___.",
        "answer": "treatable"
    },
    {
        "question": "Intelligence, common sense and a sense of humor made Laura and ideal traveling ___.",
        "answer": "companion"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whether viewed as acceptable or not, overweight and obesity are gradually becoming a ___ in America, with obesity rate of adults higher than 30%.",
        "answer": "norm"
    },
    {
        "question": "The complexity of this case may even ___ the most sophisticated lawyer.",
        "answer": "daunt"
    },
    {
        "question": "They have not been offered any financial incentive, but they have willingly and happily ___ their time and expertise, which makes their charitable contributions remarkable and influential.",
        "answer": "donated"
    },
    {
        "question": "As the captain, he knew that ___ the honor of the ship was the priority, and also knew he would lose forever the ship by taking those necessary actions.",
        "answer": "preserving"
    },
    {
        "question": "Some people experience shyness as a ___ to communication, but this can be broken down gradually.",
        "answer": "barrier"
    },
    {
        "question": "Students will be asked to monitor their own performance and ___ an analysis and evaluation of the learning they have gained.",
        "answer": "undertake"
    },
    {
        "question": "What grew chidfly upon me was the ___ that only those who are trustworhy know how to trust others.",
        "answer": "conviction"
    },
    {
        "question": "Animal welfare laws are strictly enforced in these countries and the media also ___ animal abuses very widely.",
        "answer": "publicise"
    },
    {
        "question": "For such a mysterious and profound topic, out language is inadequate and seems ___, as if someone were trying to plow with a feature.",
        "answer": "laughable"
    },
    {
        "question": "This initiative demonstrates once more our commitment to ___ a just and lasting peace.",
        "answer": "securing"
    },
    {
        "question": "Its thorough research and ___ scope should prove invaluable for anyone seriously interested in the subject.",
        "answer": "comprehensive"
    },
    {
        "question": "He is not Much of a good project leader because he lacks the ability to make ___ decisions.",
        "answer": "informed",
        "count": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "A growing number of studies show a strong association between exercise and improvements in bone mineral ___.As a living tissue, bone responds to exercise by becoming stronger and ___.",
        "answer": "density  denser"
    },
    {
        "question": "Journalists expect to be given the freedom to visit, investigate, and report without ___. However, their activities should be reasonably ___ lest the freedom be misused.",
        "answer": "constraint  constrained"
    },
    {
        "question": "Three specied of dolphin ___ in the water of New Zealand, but they are hiding today. Luckily, we have encounters with other ___ here -- seals.",
        "answer": "reside  residents"
    },
    {
        "question": "A more advanced organism, like humans, will ___ less advanced species during its development stages. However, whtat distinguished humans from other lower species is the distinction, instead of the ___.",
        "answer": "resemble  resemblance"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to a new research, mothers of ___ births had much greater odds of having moderate or servere postpartum depressive symptoms compared with mothers of single babies. A contributing factor consisted in the ___ stress from several babies.",
        "answer": "multiple  multiplied"
    },
    {
        "question": "The environmentally conscious network will soft-sell its mission, making ___ a bigger priority than education. The trush is that the majority of TV viewers want to keep it ___.",
        "answer": "entertainment  entertaining"
    },
    {
        "question": "Phone conversations have been universally regarded as an ideal ___ for face-to-face conversation. But could they ___ for pleasant chats with friends over lunch or in the pub after work?",
        "answer": "substitute  substitute"
    },
    {
        "question": "Japen's farmers argue that ___ of tariffs on all imports would destroy their livelihoods. However, the broader Japanese public is eager for lower consumer prices that would come with ___ tariffs.",
        "answer": "elimination  eliminated"
    }
]